So, here are the numbers of three companies of the futures market. All
three came after the market closed. I am
starting with ICICI Prudential. The
numbers are good, be it the premium
figures, value of new business,
value of new business, margin, everything is above
expectations. There is improvement in the margin
because the product mix has been improving. The
high margin protection business has led to
revenue mobilization. So,
good numbers for ICICI Prudential have
come from another company of the same group, the general
insurance company, ICICI Lombard's
numbers. It is being said that
you will see that the net premium and
profit figures have
reached 4.4 from what was expected, so there was
something in front of the expectations of 102-102.5.
Regarding the numbers, ICC Lombard Week
Delta Corp was mentioned. Keep in mind that the
numbers are of that season which is the
most important quarter for them.
December's high is in its place but the
seasonality in December had an advantage in those numbers.  It is
not visible in that, that is why Delta
Corp is being called weak, there is a
strong contraction in the margins,
almost around 620 points, so
disappointment Delta Corp